let exposure_set_trials = [
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Aisle_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Outfit</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Aisle', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Outfit', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Aisle_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Harmony_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Habitat</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Harmony', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Habitat', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Harmony_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Real_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Real</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Real', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Real', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Real_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Violin_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Violin</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Violin', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Violin', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Violin_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Aisle_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Outfit</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Aisle', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Outfit', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Aisle_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Harmony_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Habitat</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Harmony', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Habitat', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Harmony_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Real_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Real</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Real', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Real', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Real_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Violin_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Violin</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Violin', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Violin', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Violin_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Aisle_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Outfit</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Aisle', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Outfit', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Aisle_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Harmony_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Habitat</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Harmony', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Habitat', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Harmony_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Real_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Real</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Real', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Real', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Real_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Violin_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Violin</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Violin', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Violin', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Violin_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Aisle_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Outfit</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Aisle', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Outfit', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Aisle_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Harmony_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Habitat</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Harmony', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Habitat', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Harmony_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Real_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Real</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Real', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Real', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Real_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Violin_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Violin</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Violin', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Violin', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Violin_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Aisle_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Outfit</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Aisle', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Outfit', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Aisle_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Harmony_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Habitat</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Harmony', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Habitat', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Harmony_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Real_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Real</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Real', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Real', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Real_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Violin_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Violin</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Violin', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Violin', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Violin_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Aisle_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Outfit</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Aisle', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Outfit', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Aisle_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Harmony_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Habitat</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Harmony', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Habitat', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Harmony_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Real_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Real</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Real', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Real', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Real_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Violin_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Violin</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Violin', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Violin', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Violin_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Aisle_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Outfit</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Aisle', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Outfit', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Aisle_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Harmony_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Habitat</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Harmony', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Habitat', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Harmony_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Real_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Real</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Real', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Real', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Real_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Violin_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Violin</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Violin', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Violin', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Violin_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Aisle_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Outfit</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Aisle', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Outfit', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Aisle_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Harmony_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Habitat</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Harmony', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Habitat', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Harmony_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Real_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Real</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Real', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Real', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Real_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Violin_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Violin</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Violin', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Violin', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Violin_1.wav' }},]